大西洋帝国
第五季 第六集
你在这干什么
What you doing here?
等待
Waiting.
等你的男人吗
On your man?
等生意
For business.
什么生意做到妓院来了
What kind of business you got in a cathouse?
我的生意
My business.
你得走
You need to go.
现在
Now!
她不是他的
She's not his.
那是谁的
Then whose?
我的
Just mine.
-女士  -怎么了
- Ma'am?  - Yes?
-你为什么锁门  -我在换衣服
- Why you lock the door?  - I was changing.
我这衣服已经穿了三天了
Been in these clothes for three days.
有专门的更衣室啊
There's rooms for that.
我女孩睡觉呢 不能离开她
- My girl's asleep. I can't leave her.
听医生说
Heard from the doctor.
说什么
Yes?
他会来的 换完了把门开开
He'll come by. Unlock this when you done.
好的
I will.
走吧
Walk out.
趁你还走的了
While you can.
我们一起等医生来吧
Let's both see him.
-我还醒着  -我困死了
-I'm awake. - I ain't.
这种晚上
This kind of night...
时间慢的就好像钟表倒着走一样
it's like the clock's running backwards.
不是周末人就没那么多
The middle of the week's always slow.
你好了解啊
Look who's the expert now.
不久不就能管理这地方了
Pretty soon you'll be running the joint.
不是吧
I don't know about that.
你知道你这么大的时候我在干嘛呢
What I was doing, I was your age?
啪啪
Pow-pow.
我十六岁就有了自己的帮派了
My own gang, 16 years old.
人们都很尊重我 我那时候很成功的
People respected me. I was going places.
那怎么了呢后来
What happened?
你爸把我介绍给你妈了
Your father set me up with your mother.
-等等 他什么  -没事
- Wait. What did-- he what? - Nothing.
我确定他们每周日都会坐第一排
I'm sure they're in the front pew every Sunday.
我就拿点三明治来
Just brought the sandwiches.
小姐
Se?±or.
请开门
Las medianoches.
有吃的了
The food...?
该死的
Me cago en Dios.
他去哪了
Where did he go?
你干嘛呢
What are you doing?
草莓派
Strawberry pie.
早上再做吧
Leave it for the morning.
要坏了
They're starting to turn.
你来晚了
You came in late.
我走不了
I couldn't get out of there.
一个演讲接着一个演讲
It was just speech after speech.
-你讲了吗  -我哪能不讲啊
- Did you make one?  - I had to.
你讲了什么
What did you say?
"尊敬的各位先生们
"Respected gentlemen of the hall,
"市长大人 海军队长凯尼特利
Mr. Mayor, Commodore Kaestner"...
"作为一种义务和荣耀
"I regard it as both a duty and a privilege
"我很注重人才的推进
to put forward a man
"作为一个有取之不竭的精力的人
whose energy is unquenchable,
"品行无可怀疑的人
whose character is unimpeachable,
"怀着无限忠诚的人"
whose loyalty is inexhaustible."
结构不错
A nice construction.
"在七月四号这一天
"The next Alderman on the Fourth Ward
"向你们隆重介绍下届市议员及我儿时的好友
and boon companion of my youthful years,
"詹姆斯 派特里克 内亚力"
the Honorable James Patrick Neary."
但是呢
The thing is,
我一直觉得他只是个好水手
I've always considered him a real son of a sailor.
只要你给大家留下深刻印象就行了
As long as you made a strong impression.
他们都一直叫我纳吉
Everyone kept calling me Nucky.
-不是吧  -是啊
- Oh,no.  - Mm-hmm.
我叫纳吉 伙计们
My name's Nucky,boys.
我主管女士们 你们是干嘛的
I'm in ladies' garters. What's your line?
抽个"雪家"吧
Say,have yourself a "see-gar."
听起来这样吗
Is that what it sounds like?
怎么了
What's wrong?
你又恶心了吗
You nauseous again?
要叫医生吗
Should I fetch the doctor?
我就是睡不着
I just couldn't sleep.
晚餐的时候
I sat at that dinner
我看着他们背地里诋毁吉姆 内亚力
and watched them slap Jim Neary on the back.
他们之所以让他当市议员
They'll make him alderman
是因为海军准将想让他当
because that's what the Commodore wants.
我为他服务了13年
13 years I've served him.
都没人提我的名字
Never even says my name.
你会被认可的
You'll be recognized.
-你的努力他都看在眼里  -没事
- He'll see you're working--  - It doesn't matter.
我有你就够了
I have you.
我会成为一个父亲
I'm gonna be a father.
我会出人头地
I'll make my way.
我知道这一切的意义何在
I know what I'm doing it for.
火机们 泥们嚎啊
How-de-do,fellas?
抽颗雪家吧
Have yourselves a "see-gar."
我不喜欢烟
I don't like cigarettes.
小女孩才抽烟呢
Pissy little girlie smokes.
烟 水果酒
Cigarettes. Drinks with fruit.
手提包 熏衣草香皂之类乱七八糟的东西
Darling handbags. Lavender soap.All that cunty shit.
说说你的名字吧
Why don't you tell me your name?
弗朗西斯 X 布什曼
Francis X. Bushman.
-真的吗  -当然
-Really? -Absolutely.
X代表什么
What's the X stand for?
代表世间万物
The X will stand for pretty much anything.
弗朗西斯 X
Francis X.
弗朗西斯 X. 你来自哪里
Francis X.,where you from?
你觉得呢
Where do you think I'm from?
俄亥俄州和加州
what's that state between,uh,
中间的州是什么
Ohio and California?
遗忘之州
The state of oblivion.
你他妈是在耍我吗 弗朗西斯 X
You fucking with me,Francis X.?
-不是  -我不喜欢被耍
-No. -I don't like to be fucked with.
我没耍你
I'm not fucking with you.
那我刚才说的那个州叫什么
So what's the state I'm talking about?
-密苏里  -你就是那里人
-Missouri. -That's where you're from.
-是吗  -被你看穿了
-Isn't it? -You got me.
我很会看人的性格
I'm a good judge of character.
问问我两个前夫就知道了
Just ask my first two husbands.
他们不知道自己错过了(还有丢了的意思)什么
They didn't know what they were missing.
我带走了大约有800美元和一些玻璃首饰
About 800 bucks and some paste jewelry by the time I was done.
什么风把你吹来了 来自密苏里的弗朗西斯 X 布什曼
What brings you to our fair city,"Francis X. Bushman from Missouri"?
你说说看
Judge my character.
你是来参加什么大会的
You come for some kind of convention.
卖的是针织品或是梳子
You sell hosiery or hair combs
或者帽边的缎带 谁他妈在乎
or hatbands or who gives a fuck.
你结婚了 但是你妻子很久不和你上床了
You're married,but your wife hasn't sucked your cock since Harding bought the farm.
你以前总是和你那些狐朋狗友一块到处跑
You used to run around with your asshole pals,
周六晚上总是热血沸腾
get yourself boiled on Saturday night.
在一个妓院门口排队
Line up at the one whorehouse in town,
明明是快枪手 完事后还自圆其说
come quick,and lie about it after.
但是你现在想的是和你秘书上床
But now you're mostly thinking about fucking your secretary,
从老板那里偷一船货
stealing a boatload off your boss,
然后就纠结是站在有轨电车电车前被撞死痛还是
and whether or not it would hurt more to stand in front of a trolley
一枪打在脑袋上痛
or shoot yourself in the head.
还有 你很爱你的孩子
Oh--and you love your children.
我说得怎么样
How'd I do?
我卖的是地板蜡
I sell floor polish.
你可怜的小混蛋
Oh,you poor,sad fuck.
你到底在这里做什么
What the hell are you doing here?
希望能找点乐子
Looking for a good time.
你知道这是什么地方吗
You know what kind of place this is?
在这里 根本就
This is where hope comes
没有希望
to get fucked in the ass.
希望什么时候来
When's she showing up?
我们要是现在跑
If we run now,
安吉洛怎么会知道
how's D'Angelo gonna know?
跑去哪 怎么跑
Run where? With what?
进去房间 扔下钱
Get into the count room,drop off the money.
放下包 不要打开
Leave the satchel,don't open it.
我走出去 开始和他们聊天
I step out,start a conversation--
"谁看了小熊队的比赛吗"
"Anybody catch that Cubs game?"
我再带着钥匙回去 清空包 打开保险柜
I double back with the key,empty the satchel,open the safe.
我们没好好考虑清楚
This has not been thought through.
该死
Fuck.
我之前说过的 关于你妻子的话
What I said before,about your spouse,
是个意外...
you know,being an accident...
我没想说得那么可怕
I didn't mean it in a sense of something horrible.
叽叽咕咕什么呢
What's all the whispering?
-送货  -早上再来
-Drop-off. -Come back in the morning.
已经晚到一天了 我们想现在进去
It's already a day late. We want to get it in now.
给我
Give it to me.
我们必须确定货到了
We need to be sure it's added.
不是针对你
Nothing personal.
好吧 进来 快点
All right. Come on,hurry up.
等一下 等一下 我没有钥匙
Wait,wait,wait. I don't have the key.
知道钥匙在哪吗
You know where the key is?
在老大桌子上吗
Big Boy's desk?
去拿
Go get it.
没人敢动他桌子
No one touches the desk.
-除非他在这里  -他现在不在
-Unless he's here. -He's not here now.
我们真的需要放下这个
We really need to drop this off.
你干什么
Hey,whoa,whoa,whoa. What are you doing?
-试试能不能打开  -不能这么做
-Trying the knob. -Can't do that.
要是能打开 门就开了 是吧
If it's open,it's open,right?
我们...
We,uh...
你别动
Don't you fucking move!
你们鬼鬼祟祟干什么
What are you creeping around for?
-来送货  -那房间关着门
-A drop-off. -The room is closed.
-没上锁 所以  -里面有人占用了
-It was unlocked,so---It was occupied!
很明确里面有人占用了
It was as occupied as a room can get!
-我们来晚了  -晚了一点而已
-We were late. -Just a little late.
-上次我们迟到挨骂了  -给我
-Last time there was some concern. -Give that to me.
理论上 应该交到...
Uh,technically that's supposed to go in the,uh...
只要是交到了拉尔夫手里
Well,as long as it's in Ralph's hands,
我想没问题....
I guess it's okay to--
你们想耍什么花招
What the fuck are you trying to pull?
我们想耍什么花招
What are we trying to pull?
拉尔夫 你想我们去找他们的老大吗
Ralph,you want us to track down the Big Boy?
去找迈克 安吉洛
Go find Mike D'Angelo.
让我带她走吧 就让我带她走吧
Let me take her out of here. Just let me do that.
好让你又溜走吗
So you can book off again?
你没有来找我
You didn't come for me.
难道你有想到我吗
You the honeypot, though,ain't you?
你不能让她趟这浑水 你不是这样的人
You can't want her part of this. It's not what you are.
不根本不了解我
You don't know me, do you?
我知道你不会收手
I know you wouldn't stop.
我知道我必须离开 否则永远无法自由
I know I had to leave or never be free.
现在你自由了吗
You free now?
七年来 每天晚上我闭起双眼
Seven years I close my eyes at night.
耳边总萦绕着你的声音
Only thing got me to sleep was your voice in my head.
然后我才发现 我已经不记得你的声音了
Then I realized I didn't even remember what you sound like.
于是我幻想你的声音
Just made you up.
告诉我发生了什么事
Tell me what happened.
求求你
Please?
我们这是在哪
Where are we?
宝贝 我们在纽约
we're in New York, precious.
正如我跟你说的
Like I said we'd be.
我睡着了
I fell asleep.
是的
Yes,you did.
我能吃点什么吗
Can I have something to eat?
等我们完事后 马上给你吃的
As soon as we finish here.
要等多久
How soon is that?
不用多久
Not long.
对吗
Will it be?
你来自哪里 小不点
Where you hail from, little one?
没事的 你可以告诉他
It's okay. You can tell him.
我在俄克拉荷马州出生
I was born in Oklahoma.
但我们去过很多地方
But we've been all over.
因为你妈妈要登台唱歌吗
When your mama sing?
她不会唱歌
She doesn't sing.
那她都干什么
Then what she do?
替安格鲁先生工作
Work for Mr. Engler.
是吗 那是谁
Yeah? Who that?
他是一个在孟菲斯市的白人
He's a white man in Memphis.
她都替他做什么工作
What she do for him?
我帮他清洁厕所
I keep his toilets clean.
我求求你
I'm begging you.
你能让我进去吗
Will you let me in?
如果我不能见你 又怎么好好谈
We can't talk if I'm not able to see you.
你大老远跑来 不是为了玩这蠢游戏吧
It's a long way to travel for foolish games.
让他进来
Let him in.
去啊
Go on.
好的
Okay.
去那边坐好 别说话
Go sit over there and be quiet.
去那边坐好
Go sit over there.
我懂了
I see.
你叫什么
What's your name?
我叫奥尔西娅
My name's Althea.
真好听
That's pretty.
知道这名字什么意思吗
Do you know what it means?
在古希腊语中 是"治愈"的意思
It means "healing" in ancient Greek.
我叫瓦伦丁
My name is Valentin.
至于这人 你认识吗
And this man, do you know him?
她们与我们的事无关
They ain't a part of this.
看来 我们都有各自的私事要处理
Well,I suppose we all have our affairs to discuss.
你过得如何 格拉斯先生
How are you keeping, Mr. Glass?
看看这大海
Look at the ocean.
大海怎么了
What about it?
这颜色 在捕鱼季来临前两周呈这颜色
That color--two weeks before the season starts?
凶兆
Bad sign.
我觉得挺好的
Looks all right to me.
证明会有飓风
That's hurricane water.
-时间尚早吧  -这说明夏季会有不祥之兆
-Kind of early for that. - Bad sign for the summer.
我们只能祈求上天保佑
Let's hope for the best.
站着说话不腰疼
That's easy for you to say.
这三个半月可是我这一年的生计来源
I have three and a half months to make my living out here.
如果不能扭亏为盈 那我就惨了
If I don't turn a profit now, I don't turn one.
惨死了
At all.
即使这样 你们这些人也总是准时出现
But that never stops the lot of you showing up like clockwork.
不是吗
Does it?
何出此言
How's that?
琳赛去哪了
Where's Lindsay anyway?
警长今天很忙 所以...
Sheriff's got his hands full today,so...
有一个问题
There's a problem.
-什么问题  -这里有不少小偷
-Yes,sir? -Little thief running around.
你们得想办法
You need to get on it.
-什么  -狡猾的小淘气
-What? -Sneaky little monkey.
跟着顾客进来
Comes in right behind the customers.
一不留神 整盒伍长烟就不见了
Before you know it, makes off with a box of Caporals.
已经发生两次了
Twice now.
他有什么特征
Can you describe him?
10岁 11岁吧
10,11.
戴平顶帽 脏兮兮的家伙
Flat cap. Dirty little monkey.
行 我们会留意的
Well,we'll keep an eye out.
我为什么要付你钱
I'm giving you this why?
我誓要将那小贼逮捕归案 格拉斯先生
I vow to bring that rascal to justice, Mr. Glass.
"带上你的战争小队 普卡沃根
"Take your war-club, Puggawaugun,
还有拳击手套 明杰卡温
And your mittens, Minjekahwun,
还有你的桦木小舟 出海航行"
And your birch-canoe for sailing"...
-他肯定不行  -看他眼睛就知道了
-He's gonna blow it. -You can see it in his eyes.
"希望那黑色的沥青水
..."may pass the black pitch-water;
"将那残忍的魔术师杀害
"Slay this merciless magician,
"将人们从水深火热救出
"Save the people from the fever
"他呼吸着沼泽的空气 还有..."
"That he breathes across the fen-lands,And"--
弗朗西斯 算了吧
Oh,Francis. Give up.
我背下了整篇文章
I had to memorize the whole thing.
你这下烂货
You lowly piece of crap.
你这蛀虫
You worm.
-你这猪狗不如的  -你这臭袋鼠
-You dog. You hound. -You kangaroo.
什么
What?
你懂的 就是跳来跳去的
You know,hop,hop.
我就是袋鼠 两位好吗
I am a kangaroo. How do you do?
我的口袋里还有一只小笛子
In my pouch I have a kazoo.
你说什么呢
What the fuck are you talking about?
脱衣服
-Take your shirt off. -Huh?
你输了打赌 必须脱下点什么
You lost the bet. You got to take something off.
-快点  -你们为什么不会输
-Let's go. -How come you never lose?
我们比你聪明
We're smarter than you.
也比你年轻
And younger.
太垃圾了
Oh,this is shit.
镇上最差的酒
Worst booze in town.
应该说全新泽西州最差的酒
Worst booze in New Jersey.
去你的 艾琳
Fuck you,Irene.
你干嘛这样说
What'd you have to say that for?
因为我喜欢说
'Cause I felt like it.
你这讨厌 该死的酒鬼
You're a lousy, goddamn lush.
你还是海神的情妇呢
And you're King Neptune's consort.
差点就成了
I almost was once.
我帮海神口交
King Neptune's cocksucker.
你再说一次 我就毙了你
Try it again, I'll brain you.
我知道去哪有好酒
I know where to get the good stuff.
是吗 哪儿
Yeah? Where?
丽嘉酒店 我可以带你们去
The Ritz-Carlton. I'll walk you right in.
怎么带
And how you gonna do that?
妈妈让我准备好去游行
Mama dressed me for the parade.
他们都认识我
They know who I am there.
弗朗西斯 那你和我们混一起算什么呢
Well,then,Francis, what the fuck are you doing with us?
我认识他们 但我和他们不一样
I know them, but I'm not like them.
我更像你们
I'm like you.
-我还有小翅膀呢  -我从低做起
-I had little wings. -Start at the bottom.
白手起家 你们也一样
With nothing. You have nothing.
小小三重冠
A little tiara.
这是一个机会 你们该把握
There's an opportunity. You take it.
你们有别的选择吗
What choice do you have?
我看起来就像一个天使
I looked like an angel.
你别无选择 你们想想清楚吧
You don't have a choice. Get yourself ahead.
你们还能怎么着
What else can you do?
但这是为了什么
For what,though,huh?
为了什么
For what?
从没有人谈论过这事
No one ever talks about that.
也没人问起 为什么要...
No one ever asks. What's the point--
你赶紧闭嘴
Why don't you  shut the fuck up?
你说什么
Excuse me?
没人想听你说废话
Nobody wants to listen to your stupid shit.
我不是跟你说
I'm not talking to you.
反正我能听见 我受不了了
I can hear you anyways. I'm fucking sick of it.
那就哪凉快去哪
Then go somewhere else.
这是我的地方 我就该呆在这里
This is my place. This is where I belong.
确实是
Sure is.
这什么意思 老妓女 我会打掉你的奶子
What's that,you old whore? I'll punch your tits off.
你也是 你个鼠脸下流鬼
You,too,you squirrel-faced cunt.
你说话小心点
Why don't you watch your mouth?
你怎么不用勺子舀我的屎当饭吃
Why don't you spoon the shit out of my asshole and eat it for dinner?
你该向这些女士们道歉
I think you need to apologize to these ladies.
有本事来啊
Make me.
弗朗西斯 帮帮我们吧
Oh,Francis. Help us,please.
"小路从明亮的小屋
"Straightway from the Shining Wigwam
"直通到强大的女巫那里
Came the mighty Megissogwon,
"高大的身材 宽厚的臂膀
Tall of stature,broad of shoulder,
"从头到脚金线衣
Clad from head to foot in wampum,
"拿着嗜血武器"
armed with all his warlike weapons."
道歉
Apologize.
舔我的屁股吧 玛丽珍
Suck my dick,Mary Jane.
"所以离开海华沙
"Thus departed Hiawatha,
"到了回风巷
To the regions of the home-wind,
"到了幸福岛
To the Islands of the Blessed,
"到了波尼马王国
To the Kingdom of Ponemah,
"到了来世之地"
To the Land of the Hereafter."
看 我真记得
See? I do know it.
你最终都是赢家
Guess you win after all.
有什么奖励吗
What do I get?
你想要什么奖励
What do you want?
我想和你们俩上床
I want to fuck you both.
谁先说
Who wants to talk first?
也许你先
Maybe you.
我们...
We...
来抢钱的
came to rob the joint?
该死的混蛋
The fucking balls.
我们知道老大会出去...
We knew the Big Boy would be out and--
-骨头团队  -对 骨头团队
-Skeleton crew. -Yeah,skeleton crew.
我们觉得应该会很容易上手
Figured it'd be easy.
你们俩天才怎么想到这个主意的
How did you geniuses get that idea?
是我妻子
My wife.
你妻子让你抢阿尔 卡蓬
Your wife told you to rob Al Capone?
家庭矛盾
We're having trouble at home.
我可以作证
I can vouch for that.
你想怎么解决这件事
How you want to handle this?
别无选择是吧
Only one choice,right?
你是老大 你想亲自处理吗
You're the boss. You want to do it?
你想让我处理吗
Do you want me to do it?
还是想等阿尔来处理
Do you want to wait for Al?
先把他们弄出去
Just get 'em out of here.
-干净利落点  -交给我来处理
-Neat and quick. -That's me all over.
你还需要他们吗
You need any of these guys?
算了 老大还在外面
Nah,I got my boys outside.
-我们走吧  -去哪
-Let's go. -Where to?
跳马拉松
Dance marathon.
看看你们能撑多久
Let's see how long you can stay on your feet.
还要再来一拳吗
Do you want another one?
不用了 先生
No,sir.
去比赛吧
Off to the races.
晚上好 阿尔 回来的挺早啊
Evening,Al. You're back early.
是啊
Yeah.
#小鸭子都会嘎嘎叫...#
#Any little duck can quack...#
#小虫子都会慢慢爬#
#Any little worm can crawl#
#小鼹鼠都会在阳光下嬉戏#
#Any little mole can frolic in the sun#
#打个小洞 玩玩闹闹#
#And make a little hole and have a little fun.#
拉尔菲  认识一下我的新朋友
Ralphie,meet my new friends.
保罗 曼尼先生 乔治 拉夫特先生
Mr. Paul Muni,Mr. George Raft.
他们从加利福尼亚州好莱坞市来到这里
They've journeyed here from Hollywood,California.
梦想之地 告诉他们你为何而来 乔治
Land of dreams. Tell him why you're here,George.
我们在拍犯罪剧
We're doing a crime picture.
-在芝加哥  -对
-Set in Chicago. -That's right.
什么剧
About?
类似莎士比亚戏剧
Kind of a Shakespearean drama.
-男人的大起大落  -还加入很多打斗情节
-Man's rise and fall. -With lots of action.
他最终做到了 是吧
And he gets it in the end,right?
他们必须这么做
That's how they have to do it.
为了让他们知道是怎么回事
And to show them how that works,
我决定要将他们介绍给巴格斯 莫兰
I figured I'd introduce them to Mr. Bugs Moran.
来抽雪茄
Break open the Cubanos.
喝酒 玩个纸牌怎么样
Drinks. Let's get a card game going,huh?
你们在这干什么
What are you doing here?
我们正要走
We were just leaving.
答非所问
That's a different question.
正在处理个问题 阿尔
Taking care of a problem,Al.
什么问题
What problem?
有意思
Interesting.
你们俩自便
You two make yourselves at home.
你们俩 过来
You two,over here.
不介意的话
If you would be so kind.
你们听到了吧
You heard the man.
好 各位注意啦 走过路过别错过啦
Okay,folks,listen up. Look up,walk up,and pay up.
好啊 今天是个散步的好日子
Yes,it's a grand day to stroll the boardwalk.
但我们还有比海水沙滩更值得一看的
But we got more to see than water and sand.
只要五美分就能看到大西洋城最有特色的...
Just one nickel pays admission to Atlantic City's very own...
-你能说句话吗  -不好办
-Could you put a word in? -It's tricky.
我没想找什么 只是公寓里的一件东西
I'm not looking for much. Just something in the department.
时机不到
It needs to be the right time.
吉姆 内亚力会提名担任市议员
Jim Neary gets put up for alderman.
你想像吉姆 内亚力那样吗
You want to be like Jim Neary?
一个毫无诚信可言的家伙
Man doesn't have an honest bone in his body.
你花钱去吃那顿饭
You paid money to go to that dinner.
这两者有什么关系
What's that got to do with it?
下次你看到海军准将...
Next time you see the Commodore...
我会处理的
I'll handle it.
也许就在一个消防站了...
Well,maybe one of the firehouses--
伊莱 你得相信我 好吗
Eli,you need to trust me,okay?
纳吉
Nuck.
-纳吉  -怎么了
-Hey,Nuck. - What?
上周六
Last Sunday,
朱恩和她的父母与我一同乘坐双桅帆船
I went with June and her parents up to Brigantine.
我们沿着海滨散步的时候
We're all walking along the shore
她突然说 "我的发带丢了
and she goes, "I lost my hair ribbon.
你帮我找找"
Help me find it."
-我们在草丛后面帮她系紧发带   -伍长烟 伍长烟
-We wind up behind the grass. -Caporals! Caporals!
-她让我把手放在她的发梢  -一卷一便士 伍长烟草
-And she lets me put my hand right there. -A penny apiece. Caporals.
-先生 要烟草吗  -我不敢相信
-Hey,mister,cigarette?  - I couldn't believe it.
你会听到 他们所有人都在谈论别人
You could hear them all talking on the other--
发生了什么事
What's going on?
站住
Hey!
停下来
Stop!
小心点
Watch it!
爆米花 花生 还有小孩子的奖品
Popcorn,peanuts, and a prize for the kiddies!
只需五美分 您就可以尝尽美味
One little nickel gets you a lot of deliciousness!
就在这里 来拿您的椒盐脆饼干...
Right here, get your pretzels...
这样真的让我很受伤
This really hurts my feelings.
我对你们做过什么啊
I mean,what'd I ever do to you,huh?
我总是支持鼓励你们
Except give you a leg up?
我接纳了你
I take you in.
就是为了你的兄弟 让你能隐姓埋名
Favor to your brother so you could lay low.
我没做这些事吗
Didn't I do that?
你做了
You did.
你可曾对我说过 谢谢
You ever say thank you?
我还没听你说过呢
I never heard it.
非常...感谢
Thank you very much.
现在说 已经没意义了
Doesn't count now.
还有你
And you.
我还以为咱们是兄弟呢
I thought we was buddies.
咱们当然是兄弟 阿尔
Of course we are,Al.
你会偷兄弟的东西吗
You steal from buddies?
你这样成了什么样的家伙
What kind of a man does that make you?
贪婪
Greedy.
非常贪婪
Just very greedy.
你呢
And you?
我也很贪婪
I'm greedy,too.
我现在想的是
Here's what I'm thinking.
我不相信你们两个
I don't believe you.
你们应该在密谋着什么事情
I think you're up to something.
查理 卢西亚诺是对的
I think Charlie Luciano was right.
我觉得你应该是个该死的警察
I think you're a fucking badge.
阿尔 还有客人在
Al,you got your guests.
拉尔菲 把收音机音量调大
Turn up the radio, Ralphie.
你有什么想说的
What you have to say?
我是纳尔逊 卡斯帕 房 奥尔登
I am Nelson Kasper Van Alden!
我是美国财政部宣过誓的探员
I am a sworn agent of the United States Treasury.
我向耶稣起誓
And I swear by Jesus our Lord
正义会把你绳之以法的 如果这是我最后一次...
justice will rain down upon you if it is my last--
该死的联邦局卧底
Fucking Fed piece of shit.
把他挪开
Get him off me!
斯诺克 你没事吧
You all right,Snork?
他差点把我杀了 他差点把我杀了
He was gonna kill me. He was gonna kill me.
-差一点  -今天的广播就为您播报到这里了
He was. This concludes our broadcast day.
来自芝加哥的赫伯特 卡特尔即将与您告别
This is Herbert Carter signing off from Chicago.
一直以来 该死的
All this time. Fuck.
是卖熨斗的吗
The shit with the irons?
去死吧
Fuck! Fuck you!
-去死  -抱歉 朱恩
-Fuck! - I'm sorry,June.
-混蛋  -我很抱歉 我很抱歉
-Fucking son of a bitch. -I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
-老板 里面没事吧  我很抱歉 我很抱歉 朱恩
-Boss,you all right?  -I'm sorry. I'm sorry,June.
-没事  -你在嘟囔什么
-It's all right. -What are you mumbling?
在外面待命
Stay out.
我在跟你说话啊
I'm talking to you,huh?!
说清楚点 现在说清楚点
Spill it! Spill it now!
我们来是为了分类账簿
W-We came for the ledgers.
为什么
Why?
是别人派我们来的
We were told to.
-谁派你们来的  -联邦...
-By who? -This Fed...
我们被敲诈了
who was squeezing us.
他叫什么名字
What's his name,huh?
不管怎样 都结束了 不是吗
Look,either way it's over,huh?
告诉我 我让你死个痛快
Tell me and I'll make it quick.
这个"布洛赫"...
This "Prohee"...
名字叫内斯
named Ness.
拉尔菲 我们不是理发师吗
We was barbers,Ralphie?
是啊
Yeah?
现在我们应该在睡觉的
We would be asleep now.
在玉米地把他毙了
Face down in a cornfield.
明白 阿尔
Sure thing,Al.
我们要怎么跟他哥哥说
What do we tell his brother?
让卢西亚诺处理吧
Luciano's taking care of him.
迈克
Mike?
看紧他
Watch him.
解决掉那个人
You finish that,
阿尔想让你到西塞罗去避避风头
Al wants you to run this over to Cicero.
他现在缺乏安全感
He's not feeling safe.
你为他做的事情 他很感激你
He's very grateful for what you've done.
罗比
Lobby.
他有两个孩子
He had two kids.
我也是
So do I.
当他们问我的工作时 我会毫无羞耻心的告诉他们
When they ask what I do,I won't be ashamed to tell them.
我怎么了
What happens to me?
你认为我一无是处吗
You think I give a shit?
为自己买张车票
Buy yourself a bus ticket.
海华沙
Hiawatha?
你喜欢这装修
You like the decor?
正合我意
Just what I was looking for.
那你有什么爱好
Then what's your pleasure?
她先来 你殿后
Her first, then you.
你不喜欢我吗
You don't like me?
把最好的留到最后
Save you for last.
你想在哪做
Where do you want to do it?
就在这里
Right here.
你这脏东西
Filthy little boy.
派尼之子 说的就是我
Son of a Piney, that's me.
我还以为你来自密苏里
I thought you was from Missouri.
我是袋鼠 你们好吗
I am a kangaroo. How do you do?
我们来干下流事吧
Let's get dirty.
弗朗西斯 告诉你
Francis, just so you know,
这不是针对你的
nothing personal.
老大还在里面吗
-Boss still inside? -Mm-hmm.
这就是你想象中的画面吗
Well,is this how you imagined it?
过了这么多年 还要挟无辜 不可能
These many years? With another innocent at hand? It can't be.
你以为你能全身而退吗
You think you getting out of this?
战斗早已结束
The battle is already over.
我自愿走进来 没有武器
I walked in here on my own accord. I have no weapon.
-你的手下在外面  -这都是后来才发生的
-Your men outside. -That would all  happen after.
你在乎吗 我认为你不在乎
Does that matter to you? I don't think it does.
让小孩子离开
Send the little one out.
梅特兰特小姐就不用管吗
But not Miss Maitland?
你来这里干什么
What you come here for?
说实话吧
True,now.
我要打开它
I need to open it.
音乐室是我付的钱
I paid for the studio,
音乐 还有出版
the musicians, the pressing.
但谁也不愿意播
No one will play it.
不愿意聘请我
No one will hire me.
芝加哥是这样 堪萨斯城也是
Not in Chicago. Not in Kansas City.
-谁也不愿意雇用我  -这与我何干
-Not anywhere. -What have I to do with that?
你让他们别再阻挡我
You stopped them to stop me.
是让我联系那些低级舞场和小酒店吗
My reach extends to every honky-tonk and barrelhouse?
我不能再像这样地活着 不能让她受苦
I can't live that way. Not with her.
把她送人 换了别人就会这样
Give her up. Others do.
你这是要逼死我
You are drowning me.
一步步把我逼死
Drop by drop.
也许是你自身原因导致失败
Perhaps the failing is your own.
你就是不愿意放过我吗
Won't you let me go?
我刚在城里开会 就赶来...
I came here from a meeting downtown--
应该说 我是被召来的
more truthful to say I was summoned--
卢西亚诺先生让我来的
with a Mr. Luciano.
我记得他
I remember him.
他让我复述条件
I am being dictated terms.
他会允许我继续做生意
I will be allowed to conduct my business,
但必须由他掌权
but only under his control.
以此作为交换 他就保护我不受他们这类人的骚扰
In exchange, I will be protected from others of his kind.
他允许我
He will allow me
在我的地盘做生意
to conduct my business in my home.
这可真是闻所未闻
This is the new order of things.
-与我无关  -如果有关呢
-Ain't no concern of mine. -What if it were?
难道我比那些背叛你的恶魔更甚吗
And am I worse than those devils who betrayed you?
我只知道你是恶魔
You the only devil I know.
随便你怎么说 但我从没认为自己是你的朋友
Call me what you will. I never claimed to be your friend.
你可以当我的手下
I'll make a place for you.
我会给你好价钱
I'll pay you well.
但如果你要复仇
If it's blood you want,
那你就白白浪费了这个好机会
you'll have your chance to spill it.
要我帮你
Me help you?
是你帮自己
You help yourself.
这房间里的所有人都想得到自由
Every soul in this room yearns to be free.
播唱片
Put the record on.
我这是在给你机会 你不会得到更好的机会
I'm making you an offer. You'll not get a better one.
播吧
Put it on.
我接受
I'll take the bargain.
不
No.
这与我无关
Don't really matter to me.
这不是我的来意
It's not what I came for.
你是来说出自己的想法 我已经听见了
You came to be heard. That's your voice.
你准备妥当 我以后就听你的
You set it up and I belong to you.
你选个城市 我打一通电话
Pick the city. I'll make the call.
你明天就要上班
You'll be booked tomorrow.
你生存的目的不是为了当白人的佣人
You weren't put on this earth to be no ofay's maid.
你不能相信他
You can't trust him.
你还不明白吗
Don't you know that?
我觉得能 有限度的相信吧
I say I can. Far as I need to.
你见过你爸爸吗
You ever meet your daddy?
妈妈很爱他 但她非走不可
Mama loved him, but she had to leave.
宝贝
Baby girl...
你千万别离开自己的妈妈 听到了吗
you stay real close to your mama now,you hear?
别让她靠近像我这样的男人
Keep her away from men like me.
我们说正事吧
Let's get to business.
给我你的枪 来证明你对我的忠诚
I'll need the gun. As a gesture of loyalty.
她们先走了
They leave first.
我们可以一起走
We'll all go together.
这是为了什么呢
What sense that make?
我们的路已经各不相同
We headed in different places.
去吧
Go on,now.
需要帮忙吗 女士
Help with that, ma'am?
你当然需要
Yes,of course you do.
我们的合作正式开始
Our collaboration begins.
爸爸想见你
Pop wants to see you.
为什么 他等钱用吗
Why,does he need money?
-不是这样的  -那是为什么
-It's not like that. -Then what?
他只有两个儿子
He's only got two sons.
我能见到妈妈 这才是最重要的
I see Ma, that's what matters.
他总是提起你
Talks about you all the time.
叫他去死
Fuck him.
别这么说
Don't use words like that.
梅布尔怀孕了
Mabel's pregnant.
是吗
She is?
那真的太好了
Well,that's bully.
站住
Hold on there.
好了 好了
All right. All right.
冷静 我们不会伤害你
Calm down. No one's gonna hurt you.
我们只是抓住了你而已
You're caught, that's all.
看来你今天挺忙的
Been busy today,hmm?
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
你肯定有个名字吧
You must have a name.
内丽 布赖
Nellie Bly.
在我面前 别耍花招
Don't cut shines with me.
书上是这么说的
That's what it says on the book.
我是纳吉
I'm Nucky.
这是我兄弟伊莱
That's my brother Eli.
我们不是你想的坏人 把名字告诉我们
It's not as bad as you think. Just tell me your name.
基利安
Gillian.
这不像是男孩的名字
That's not a name for a boy.
我不是男孩
I'm not a boy.
你他妈在看什么
Fuck you looking at?
你以为我不知道你是谁吗
You think I don't know who you are?
你这个可恶的小偷
You little thieving monkey.
我会把你赶出城的
I'll run you out of town.
什么
What?
你还想让我帮你一把吗
You expect some kind of favor?
你这个愚蠢的家伙
You stupid fucking child.
你为什么要相信我
Why would you trust me?
我不懂您的意思
I don't understand.
送我去老蓝帕斯猫  50块
Old Rumpus. $50.
听到了吗 我给你五十块
You hear me? I'll give you 50.
我说了会给你钱
I said I'll pay you.
您不用付钱给我 先生 我本来就是你的手下
You don't have to pay me,sir. I already work for you.
有人来找你
To see you.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
乔 哈勃尔
Joe Harper.
从哪来的
Where from?
印第安纳
Indiana.
你来这里做什么
What are you doing here?
想获得成功
Trying to get ahead.
你今晚看到的...
What you saw tonight--
-我什么都没看到  -你看到了我
-I didn't see anything. -You saw me.
听到了我说的话
Anything I might have said--
您说您想回家
You just said you wanted to go home.
拿着
Take it.
不 先生
No,sir.
-为什么  -今晚您也过得不如意
-Why not? -You just had a rough night.
只是这样而已
That's all.
而且 需要帮助的人来伸出援手
Besides,if you only help people to help yourself,
这个世界都成什么样了
what kind of world would it be?
与我关系亲密的一个人
Someone I was close to just died
因为我而死了
because of me.
我听到她说的最后一句话是
Last thing I heard her say was,
"这是你的咖啡"
"Have your coffee."
她走了
She's gone
而我还在这里
and I'm still here.
这个世界都成什么样了
What kind of world is that?
快拿着吧 这不是在帮你
Come on,now. It's not helping yourself.
是让我好过一点
It's helping me.
先生
Senor?
他们在楼下等你
They are downstairs.
什么
What?
所有人都给我听好了
I need everybody to listen good.
你们都曾发誓 要誓死对
You will swear an oath of allegiance
新泽西州 亚特兰大市 纳吉 汤普森先生效忠
to Mr. Nucky Thompson of Atlantic City,New Jersey,
保护他以及他的财产免受
to protect and defend his person and property against all enemies,
国内外任何敌人的侵犯 至死方休
foreign and domestic,as long as you both shall live.
没有人知道您去哪里了 我召集了大家
Nobody knew where you were. So I done a Paul Revere.
今晚要准备决一死战了吗
We saddling up for a showdown or not?
没错
We are.
把车开过来
Bring the car around.
你不去阻止他们吗 那些白人
You ain't never gonna stop them white boys.
为什么这么说
Why do you say that?
他们出动了 而你还在这里
They everywhere. You just here.
幸存即是胜利
I'd call surviving a victory.
你还挺会自圆其说的
Well,you pretty slick at that.
你要遵守对她的承诺吗
Gonna keep your word to her?
因为我会遵守的
'Cause I'm keeping to mine.
你怎么知道我不遵守
How will you know?
我不知道
I won't.
那你就认为 我也会遵守吧
Then tell yourself I will.
一切的开始都是一场梦
All a dream to begin with.
没有人是生而自由的
Ain't nobody ever been free.
那好吧
All right,then.